Oh Holy Spirit, contact my heart!
Communicate yourself.
Prayer
Every spirit that is not of God,
begin to deliver them, break them!
Evey spirit!
Every demonic influence, every demonic being
Say out!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Who are you?
I am a spirit of old woman.
Stand up! and sit down.
Who are you?
I am the spirit of old woman!
(The man says that he is a spirit of old woman.)
You are a spirit of what?
Old woman.
What are you upto?
To destroy.
How old are you?
I'm 90 years old.
How did the spirit enter you?
It entered me near the river.
Two men took me near the river to initiate me.
(The man said the spirit inside
him entered him near the river.)
I want to destroy him,
I have seven powers.
The first power to destroy his business
He thinks that he can repair laptops very well.
(Watch the screen, that is the man under deliverance
in the power of Holy Spirit.
See him manifesting
Get him out!
Okay, leave the place.
Old woman, where are you going?
Old woman, how are you?
I am fine.
Where are you?
You said you are an old woman.
No, I'm not an old woman.
You said you are 90 years old?
No, I am not 90 years old.
But you said you are an old woman.
Am not old.
What carried you from out, you are inside.
I dont know how I got here
You don't know the thing that carried you?
You see,
the whole thing is mystery, he say he is not the one
What is your name?
I am Muhammad
See your self
Who is he?
Muhammad
I dont know when I was doing this
I know that i was sitting at the back
But who is this?
Is it you?
I'm the one.
I don't know how it happened?
I don't even know how I got here sir.
But look at yourself.
If you heard yourself saying that you are an old woman,
what would you do?
I will feel embarrassed because
I am not an old woman.
Its Muhammad that is standing here,
I couldn't believe that such things
like this could happen to me.
Ive been saying that Id not be
in any church where id fall down.
I thought that falling in church is just pretending.
But i have felt it today,
I believe that there are my friend
that we have been arguing together
that all this falling down is just fake.
Because I was sitting down at the back,
I didn't know what came over me,
i just opened my eyes and i saw myself on the floor,
in front of the altar
Now falling down is real?
Yes, I believe it now.
Emmanuel!
My name is Hussein Muhammad.
From Edo state Nigeria.
The problem that brought me to SCOAN
is the problem of the demon of old woman.
Over two years now I have
been experiencing this old woman.
Anytime I slept, I discovered that an old woman
would come and make love to me in dream.
Whenever this old woman is coming,
its either my picture in my parlour would fall down
In the morning I would meet it on the floor.
When I still went to the office, i would still meet the
same picture in my office has fallen down.
Anytime this woman came, things
become very difficult for me
I couldn't do anything.
I have been going to many places -
churches, night vigil
All the people would fall but I would still stand.
That is why anytime somebody say, I would fall in church, I wouldn't actually believe it.
My younger brother has been asking me to come to Lagos that there is solution.
Anytime I went to get the ticket, something would
happen and I would leave the ticket.
Sometimes I would come and given seat number 14,
I would say I don't want number 14.
I would go back home.
Later when I made up my mind,
I sent one of my friends to buy ticket
Which he bought, and I came to Lagos and on Sunday,
and we came to this place.
When we came I was sitting at the back.
I didn't know what really happened,
I know that we were praying.
That we were saying, "Holy Spirit communicate in our heart."
That is what I knew, the next thing I
found myself in front of the altar.
This old woman has really destroyed
plenty of things in my life.
Since then, things have not been working at all.
Anything I put my hand on, it will not work at all.
After that service that day, I was delivered.
Since my deliverance, I have never
experience that old woman.
If you look at me, you see that I am shinning already.
[clapping]